const THEMES = {

    // displayname => replace "_" with " " and css capitalize
    WHITE: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#e8e8e8",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#d0d0d0",
        "--key-color-front": "#b6b6b6",
        "--key-color-side": "#a2a2a2",
        "--key-color-back": "#919191",
        "--key-font-color": "#000000"
    },
    DARK: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#2a2a2a",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#1c1c1c",
        "--key-color-front": "#151515",
        "--key-color-side": "#0c0c0c",
        "--key-color-back": "#000000",
        "--key-font-color": "#c0cae1"
    },
    CATPPUCCIN_MOCHA: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#3b405e",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#2e324b",
        "--key-color-front": "#282b41",
        "--key-color-side": "#1e2131",
        "--key-color-back": "#171926",
        "--key-font-color": "#C6D0F5"
    },
    CATPPUCCIN_LIGHT: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#C5CFF5",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#bfc7ec",
        "--key-color-front": "#B7BDF8",
        "--key-color-side": "#8AADF4",
        "--key-color-back": "#6e99d2",
        "--key-font-color": "#4b4546"
    },
    CLEAN_WHITE:{
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#D0D8E0",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#BEC8D0",
        "--key-color-front": "#afb5bb",
        "--key-color-side": "#909898",
        "--key-color-back": "#808888",
        "--key-font-color": "#303030"
    },
    HIGH_CONTRAST: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#000000",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#212121",
        "--key-color-front": "#3a3a3a",
        "--key-color-side": "#2c2c2c",
        "--key-color-back": "#111111",
        "--key-font-color": "#FFFFFF"

    },
    SILVER: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#BAB9BE",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#A0A0A5",
        "--key-color-front": "#82858E",
        "--key-color-side": "#434346",
        "--key-color-back": "#343635",
        "--key-font-color": "#000000"
    },
    FOREST_MIST: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#7DAE9E",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#6A9A8B",
        "--key-color-front": "#5C8D76",
        "--key-color-side": "#3A5A40",
        "--key-color-back": "#2F3E46",
        "--key-font-color": "#E0E0E0"
    },
    LAVENDER_DREAMS: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#E0B0FF",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#C18EE0",
        "--key-color-front": "#9A8CFF",
        "--key-color-side": "#7B68EE",
        "--key-color-back": "#6747da",
        "--key-font-color": "#FFFFFF"
    },
    DEEP_OCEAN: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#64B5F6",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#42A5F5",
        "--key-color-front": "#1E88E5",
        "--key-color-side": "#1565C0",
        "--key-color-back": "#0D47A1",
        "--key-font-color": "#FFFFFF"
    },
    BACK_IN_THE_OLD_DAYS: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#D4D3BF",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#D6D0C0",
        "--key-color-front": "#B0AE97",
        "--key-color-side": "#888566",
        "--key-color-back": "#646048",
        "--key-font-color": "#000000"
    },
    DEBUG: {
        "--key-font-color": "#FFFFFF",
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#3A86FF",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#2667E0",
        "--key-color-front": "#4CAF50",
        "--key-color-side": "#FF6B6B",
        "--key-color-back": "#FFD700",
    },
    GOLD: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#dab438",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#c5a028",
        "--key-color-front": "#b69121",
        "--key-color-side": "#a78f19",
        "--key-color-back": "#987110",
        "--key-font-color": "#ffffff"
    },
    I_AM_FROM_AUSTRIA: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#FFF",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#FFF",
        "--key-color-front": "#c9072a",
        "--key-color-side": "#FFF",
        "--key-color-back": "#c9072a",
        "--key-font-color": "#c9072a"
    },
    BLACK_AND_WHITE: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#ffffff",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#e0e0e0",
        "--key-color-front": "#b0b0b0",
        "--key-color-side": "#808080",
        "--key-color-back": "#404040",
        "--key-font-color": "#000000"
    },
    BLACK_AND_YELLOW: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#1a1a1a",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#1a1a1a",
        "--key-color-front": "#e1bf0a",
        "--key-color-side": "#d0b005",
        "--key-color-back": "#968002",
        "--key-font-color": "#ffffff"
    },
    ADULT_SITE_THEME: {
        "--key-color-top-prim": "#1b1b1b",
        "--key-color-top-sec": "#252525",
        "--key-color-front": "#ff7d22",
        "--key-color-side": "#ff6600",
        "--key-color-back": "#ff4400",
        "--key-font-color": "#ffffff"
    }
}